techpinger.com 2013-05-21

# Privacy Policy | Tech Pinger

September 10, 2009 By [Leave a Comment](http://techpinger.com/2009/09/privacy-policy/#comments)

[TechPinger.com](http://techpinger.com/) takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

#### Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

This website does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

_DoubleClick DART Cookie_  
\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy/ads](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Clickbank

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [http://techpinger.com](http://techpinger.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

This website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.thiswebsite.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

#### Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you can contact us from [Contact Page](http://techpinger.com/contact/) for further clarification.
